# Shyanne Williams 8 2<sup>nd</sup> street East, Cazabon Trincity. <a href="mailto:shyannemiya@gmail.com">shyannemiya@gmail.com</a>

### 3206685

### **Human Resource Department**

To whom it may concern,

Kindly accept this application from a talented and capable applicant who wishes to apply for a position in your institution. I am highly talented and experienced in customer service with employment in job was as a data entry clerk in RBC Royal Bank St Augustine through Recruitment Xperts limited as well as Digicel's Head Office. With my practical experience and a track record of success I am confident that I can become a top performer at your company.

I have an ability to grow with a job, handle responsibility and build positive relationships with work colleagues at all levels. You will find me to be a reliable person who has a professional, calm and honest approach to all work related matters. Technically minded and with good problem resolution skills, I am able to work effectively in fast paced and ever changing environments.

For additional information about my capabilities please view my attached resume. I thank you sincerely for taking the time to read my application, and I very much look forward to an opportunity to speak to you in more detail regarding this position.

Sincerely,

Shyanne Williams

# Shyanne Williams 8 2<sup>nd</sup> street East, Cazabon Trincity. shyannemiya@gmail.com

### 3206685

Meticulous, excellent at juggling multiple tasks and working under pressure. Self-motivated, determined, dependable and a fast learner.

#### **Work History**

- Sales clerk at Shoeaholics- Farfan Street, Arima July2013- August 2013
- Community Based Researcher at the University of the West Indies, St. Augustine,
   Department of Geography –October 2014
- Student Assistant at Admissions, U.W.I-November 2014-2015
- Data entry clerk at Rbc Royal bank- August 2016-september 2016
- Fulfilment Agent at Digicel-November 2016-present

#### **Education**

University of the West Indies- September 2014-present

Perusing a Msc in Food Science and Technology as a Part time student

St. George's College Barataria-September 2012-July 2014

#### **Academic Qualifications**

o **C.X.C** 

Biology-Grade 3

# Shyanne Williams 8 2<sup>nd</sup> street East, Cazabon Trincity. <a href="mailto:shyannemiya@gmail.com">shyannemiya@gmail.com</a>

## 3206685

Caribbean History-Grade 2

Chemistry-Grade 2

English A-Grade 2

English B-Grade1

Food and Nutrition-Grade 1

Mathematics-Grade 3

Social Studies-Grade 2

Spanish-Grade 2

#### o **C.A.P.E**

Communication Studies-Grade 2

Caribbean Studies-Grade 2

Chemistry Unit 1 –Grade 4

Chemistry Unit 2-Grade 3

Sociology Unit 1-Grade 2

Sociology Unit 2-Grade 3

Spanish Unit 1-Grade 2

Spanish Unit 2-Grade 2

# Shyanne Williams 8 2<sup>nd</sup> street East, Cazabon Trincity. <a href="mailto:shyannemiya@gmail.com">shyannemiya@gmail.com</a>

3206685